[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "You know, I'm a little nervous, so how do you do that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "little", "nervous", ",", "so", "how", "do", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "You look them in the eye.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "look", "them", "in", "the", "eye", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJR", "IN", "RB", "VBD", "``", "JJ", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 44, "question": "What -- what is your favorite movie, Mr. President?", "question_tokens": ["What", "--", "what", "is", "your", "favorite", "movie", ",", "Mr.", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Well, the first movie I ever saw more than once was \"High Noon.\"", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "movie", "I", "ever", "saw", "more", "than", "once", "was", "``", "High", "Noon", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Later on, did you realize that that was an anti-McCarthy movie?", "question_tokens": ["Later", "on", ",", "did", "you", "realize", "that", "that", "was", "an", "anti-McCarthy", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "And that all the townspeople run and hide, and there you are to face the enemy all by your lonesome?", "question_tokens": ["And", "that", "all", "the", "townspeople", "run", "and", "hide", ",", "and", "there", "you", "are", "to", "face", "the", "enemy", "all", "by", "your", "lonesome", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "CC", "VB", ",", "CC", "EX", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Sometimes.", "answer_tokens": ["Sometimes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "Who would you want to play you, Mr. President?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "you", "want", "to", "play", "you", ",", "Mr.", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Gosh, I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "George Clooney?", "question_tokens": ["George", "Clooney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "Too good looking.", "answer_tokens": ["Too", "good", "looking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Clooney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNS", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 96, "question": "What was the name of the movie?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "name", "of", "the", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "\"Descendants.\"", "answer_tokens": ["``", "Descendants", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "And Hillary, who would you play Hillary in this movie?", "question_tokens": ["And", "Hillary", ",", "who", "would", "you", "play", "Hillary", "in", "this", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "LINTON: Meryl Streep.", "answer_tokens": ["LINTON", ":", "Meryl", "Streep", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 123, "question": "Is that true or was it your idea?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "true", "or", "was", "it", "your", "idea", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 124, "answer": "No, he invited me to play.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "invited", "me", "to", "play", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "He did?", "question_tokens": ["He", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":"], "qSentId": 127, "question": "Invited you to play?", "question_tokens": ["Invited", "you", "to", "play", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "And --", "answer_tokens": ["And", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "And what possessed you to do that in the middle of a presidential race?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "possessed", "you", "to", "do", "that", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "a", "presidential", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "Well, I started -- I hadn't played in a couple of years.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "started", "--", "I", "had", "n't", "played", "in", "a", "couple", "of", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "And doesn't he realize how un-cool he is?", "question_tokens": ["And", "does", "n't", "he", "realize", "how", "un-cool", "he", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "I don't know, you know, Donald Trump has been uncommonly nice to Hillary and me.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Donald", "Trump", "has", "been", "uncommonly", "nice", "to", "Hillary", "and", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "Do you think Mitt Romney would have pulled the trigger if he was the president?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "Mitt", "Romney", "would", "have", "pulled", "the", "trigger", "if", "he", "was", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "I don't know that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Was it a mistake politically, you know, to come out in support of it?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "a", "mistake", "politically", ",", "you", "know", ",", "to", "come", "out", "in", "support", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, I think, yes, it was somewhat risky because a lot of his African-American support in the churches are not for it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", ",", "yes", ",", "it", "was", "somewhat", "risky", "because", "a", "lot", "of", "his", "African-American", "support", "in", "the", "churches", "are", "not", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "The race between Obama and Romney, how close do you think that race will be?", "question_tokens": ["The", "race", "between", "Obama", "and", "Romney", ",", "how", "close", "do", "you", "think", "that", "race", "will", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Can't tell you.", "answer_tokens": ["Ca", "n't", "tell", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "LINTON: Because of the condition of the economy.", "answer_tokens": ["LINTON", ":", "Because", "of", "the", "condition", "of", "the", "economy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "It seems to play with a certain group, but do you think that really will affect people and think that he can produce jobs that the president can't?", "question_tokens": ["It", "seems", "to", "play", "with", "a", "certain", "group", ",", "but", "do", "you", "think", "that", "really", "will", "affect", "people", "and", "think", "that", "he", "can", "produce", "jobs", "that", "the", "president", "ca", "n't", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "I think it will affect some people who relate well to businessmen.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "will", "affect", "some", "people", "who", "relate", "well", "to", "businessmen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 238, "question": "Tell us what you're planning to do this year, Mr. President?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "us", "what", "you", "'re", "planning", "to", "do", "this", "year", ",", "Mr.", "President", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 239, "answer": "Well, we're going to bring in people from all over the country to talk about the American economy.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "bring", "in", "people", "from", "all", "over", "the", "country", "to", "talk", "about", "the", "American", "economy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "Do you think we can, you know, fix the economy?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "we", "can", ",", "you", "know", ",", "fix", "the", "economy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "How do we fix it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "fix", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "But -- well, we've got to continue to accelerate the resolution of the home mortgage crisis.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "--", "well", ",", "we", "'ve", "got", "to", "continue", "to", "accelerate", "the", "resolution", "of", "the", "home", "mortgage", "crisis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJS", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "How do we go about doing that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "we", "go", "about", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "The best way to do it is for America to join most other countries in using not just tax dollars to build roads and bridges and new water systems, and infrastructure is also a new electrical grid.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "best", "way", "to", "do", "it", "is", "for", "America", "to", "join", "most", "other", "countries", "in", "using", "not", "just", "tax", "dollars", "to", "build", "roads", "and", "bridges", "and", "new", "water", "systems", ",", "and", "infrastructure", "is", "also", "a", "new", "electrical", "grid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "What are we planning to do about fixing education in this country?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "we", "planning", "to", "do", "about", "fixing", "education", "in", "this", "country", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, I think there are two things you have to do.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "are", "two", "things", "you", "have", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Can you tell the American people why you think the economy went bad in the United States?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "tell", "the", "American", "people", "why", "you", "think", "the", "economy", "went", "bad", "in", "the", "United", "States", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "Well, I think two things happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "two", "things", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "And they repealed the oversight bills, didn't they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "they", "repealed", "the", "oversight", "bills", ",", "did", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, they -- to some extent.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "--", "to", "some", "extent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 308, "question": "How do you feel about what he -- what he did today?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "what", "he", "--", "what", "he", "did", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 309, "answer": "I think he's doing the right thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "the", "right", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBD", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 331, "question": "How did you get there, and how do I get there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "get", "there", ",", "and", "how", "do", "I", "get", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "EX", ",", "CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 332, "answer": "Well, what I did was -- first of all, when I had my second heart incident and I had to put the stents put in, I had passed all my physicals, I was doing great, I was still building up plaque in my arteries.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "I", "did", "was", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "when", "I", "had", "my", "second", "heart", "incident", "and", "I", "had", "to", "put", "the", "stents", "put", "in", ",", "I", "had", "passed", "all", "my", "physicals", ",", "I", "was", "doing", "great", ",", "I", "was", "still", "building", "up", "plaque", "in", "my", "arteries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary"]}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "What would you do in this situation, and what would you advise the president?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "in", "this", "situation", ",", "and", "what", "would", "you", "advise", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Well, I think that the president -- and, you know, Hillary as secretary of state has been very actively in this.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "president", "--", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Hillary", "as", "secretary", "of", "state", "has", "been", "very", "actively", "in", "this", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Is the world better without Assad?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "world", "better", "without", "Assad", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I think so, now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", ",", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "You were able to hold it together?", "question_tokens": ["You", "were", "able", "to", "hold", "it", "together", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "I was, for two reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", ",", "for", "two", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "How did you raise a teenager in the White House?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "raise", "a", "teenager", "in", "the", "White", "House", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "As much as possible we raised her as we would have if we hadn't been in the White House.", "answer_tokens": ["As", "much", "as", "possible", "we", "raised", "her", "as", "we", "would", "have", "if", "we", "had", "n't", "been", "in", "the", "White", "House", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "You watched \"The Princess Bride\" with Chelsea, what, every year?", "question_tokens": ["You", "watched", "``", "The", "Princess", "Bride", "''", "with", "Chelsea", ",", "what", ",", "every", "year", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "IN", "NNP", ",", "WP", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Oh yes, we've watched it, I don't know, countless times.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "yes", ",", "we", "'ve", "watched", "it", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", ",", "countless", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chelsea"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "Chelsea, Hillary?", "question_tokens": ["Chelsea", ",", "Hillary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Chelsea will be too young, I think, maybe not quite.", "answer_tokens": ["Chelsea", "will", "be", "too", "young", ",", "I", "think", ",", "maybe", "not", "quite", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hillary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clinton"]}, "docId": "120603pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Mr. President, the Clinton Global Initiative, how do the viewers, you know, who are watching tonight, how do they get involved?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "President", ",", "the", "Clinton", "Global", "Initiative", ",", "how", "do", "the", "viewers", ",", "you", "know", ",", "who", "are", "watching", "tonight", ",", "how", "do", "they", "get", "involved", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Well, they can go to our Web site, ClintonFoundation.org, or there is one of the Clinton Global Initiative, CGI.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "can", "go", "to", "our", "Web", "site", ",", "ClintonFoundation.org", ",", "or", "there", "is", "one", "of", "the", "Clinton", "Global", "Initiative", ",", "CGI", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. President", "Clinton"]}}]